<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Miguel</title>
 <link href="miguelis.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="miguelis.me/"/>
 <updated>2016-02-19T18:38:43-05:00</updated>
 <id>miguelis.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Miguel Ocampo-Gooding</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>CUSEC</title>
   <link href="miguelis.me/2016/01/27/cusec/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>miguelis.me/2016/01/27/cusec</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;h1&gt;CUSEC 2016&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;ve been a part of CUSEC for 4 years but I want to focus on the last year that I was
involved with the conference.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2016, I volunteered as the designer and webmaster. For this year, I wanted
to go for a look that was traditional and clean but also had some funky colors.
I decided to take inspiration from CUSEC 2014 and give it a splash of color that
I thought would give the conference a great look.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Developing the website was a great time. The CUSEC 2014 website had a great layout
that was simple and easy to reproduce. The chairs asked that I didn&amp;#39;t use a
hamburger icon button in the mobile view. &lt;a href=&quot;http://builtbybuffalo.com/&quot;&gt;Built
By Buffalo&lt;/a&gt; has a beautiful website and a great nav that did exactly what I wanted.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the website here. &lt;a href=&quot;2016.cusec.net&quot;&gt;2016.cusec.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I also had to design the sponsorship and conference booklets. It was great to see
the conference booklets printed and in the hands of everyone at the conference. &lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>UAV-g Conference</title>
   <link href="miguelis.me/2015/12/24/uavg/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>miguelis.me/2015/12/24/uavg</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2014, I was given my first paid job as a web developer. I
developed the website for the 2015 Unmanned Aerial Vehicle for Geomatics conference
that was held at York University. I&amp;#39;ve made simple websites before but never for
a global audience. This was also my first experience working with a client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went into it with big ideas and I wanted to make it look flashy, cool, and sexy.
After having looked at the previous years websites, I wanted to go in a different
direction. Let&amp;#39;s throw in some color, make it a one pager and have the elements
animated in some shape or form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the project, I learned a lot from my mistakes. The most notable mistakes
was not being able to understand what I did when I look at the code after a few weeks
of inactivity, focusing on cool ideas instead of focusing on delivering the content
in an easy to read way, and making the website mobile friendly. These were all
new concepts to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website was built using Bootstrap and JQuery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the website here &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.uav-g-2015.ca&quot;&gt;uav-g-2015.ca&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Submitago</title>
   <link href="miguelis.me/2015/12/24/submitago/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>miguelis.me/2015/12/24/submitago</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Submitago is a RoR project developed for my User Interface class. It wasn&amp;#39;t a requirement
to make a functioning app but I thought it&amp;#39;d be a fun exercise to see how designing a UI
would translate to actually developing the application.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This was my first exposure working with RoR. Submitago was designed to be
a moodle clone that improved the UI of moodle while maintaining its basic
functionality. My team found that moodle was too cluttered and wasn&amp;#39;t an enjoyable
application to use.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Working with RoR was such a nice experience. It&amp;#39;s so easy to set up a new project and
to create databases. Things just make sense and easy to fly through the development
process.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;RoR A++ would code again.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Good Morning Mirror</title>
   <link href="miguelis.me/2015/12/24/mirror/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>miguelis.me/2015/12/24/mirror</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This project was my first experience working with Javascript. I decided to create
a smart mirror built with Javascript, Annyang.js, and Bootstrap. It was a fun
experience as it got me exposed to working with Javascript and using libraries
that I haven&amp;#39;t been exposed to. It also had me think about how the user would
experience the mirror. What would they use it for? What would they want to see?
How should they interact with the mirror? This was a problem that I encountered
during my development. Initially, I used a LeapMotion to interact with the mirror.
I thought that a person could wave their hand around the mirror to do certain functions.
As development went on, I found that using the LeapMotion required the user to be
active in order for the mirror to work properly. I switched from LeapMotion to using Annyang.js
so that the user can speak to the mirror to use it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the code here &lt;a href=&quot;github.com/mirror&quot;&gt;Good Morning Mirror Project&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
