<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>Miguel</title>
 <link href="http://miguelis.me/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://miguelis.me/"/>
 <updated>2016-01-27T16:25:50-05:00</updated>
 <id>http://miguelis.me</id>
 <author>
   <name>Miguel Ocampo-Gooding</name>
   <email></email>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>CUSEC</title>
   <link href="http://miguelis.me/2016/01/27/cusec/"/>
   <updated>2016-01-27T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://miguelis.me/2016/01/27/cusec</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I started volunteering for CUSEC back in 2014 as a head delegate for York University.
As a head delegate, I brought about 15 students to Montreal for CUSEC.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2015, I volunteered on the design team and led a team to create posters,
booklets, and the logo. Everything that the sponsors, speakers, and delegates
saw and touched, my team made.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For 2016, I was brought back to volunteer as the web and design team. I performed
the same responsibilities as the year before along with developing the 2016 website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Check out the website here. &lt;a href=&quot;2016.cusec.net&quot;&gt;2016.cusec.net&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>UAV-g Conference</title>
   <link href="http://miguelis.me/2015/12/24/uavg/"/>
   <updated>2015-12-24T00:00:00-05:00</updated>
   <id>http://miguelis.me/2015/12/24/uavg</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;In the summer of 2014, I was given my first paid job as a web developer. I
developed the website for the 2015 Unmanned Aerial Vehicle for Geomatics conference
that was held at York University. I&amp;#39;ve made simple websites before but never for
a global audience. This was also my first experience working with a client.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I went into it with big ideas and I wanted to make it look flashy, cool, and sexy.
After having looked at the previous years websites, I wanted to go in a different
direction. Let&amp;#39;s throw in some color, make it a one pager and have the elements
animated in some shape or form.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the project, I learned a lot from my mistakes. The most notable mistakes
was not being able to understand what I did when I look at the code after a few weeks
of inactivity, focusing on cool ideas instead of focusing on delivering the content
in an easy to read way, and making the website mobile friendly. These were all
new concepts to me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This website was built using Bootstrap and JQuery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can see the website here &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.uav-g-2015.ca&quot;&gt;uav-g-2015.ca&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>
